{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Which country does the band Rammstein hail from?",
            "correct_answer": "Germany",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Austria",
                "Armenia",
                "Belgium"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Which one of these songs did the group &quot;Men At Work&quot; NOT make?",
            "correct_answer": "Safety Dance",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Down Under",
                "Who Can It Be Now?",
                "It&#039;s a Mistake"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "The 2016 song &quot;Starboy&quot; by Canadian singer The Weeknd features which prominent electronic artist?",
            "correct_answer": "Daft Punk",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "deadmau5",
                "Disclosure",
                "DJ Shadow"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "What 1970&#039;s American ballad referred to the 1959 plane crash as the &quot;the day the music died&quot;?",
            "correct_answer": "American Pie",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Kentucky Rain",
                "I Will Always Love You",
                "Rock &#039;n&#039; Roll Suicide"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Who is the lead singer of the British pop rock band Coldplay?",
            "correct_answer": "Chris Martin",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Jonny Buckland",
                "Guy Berryman",
                "Will Champion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Kanye West&#039;s &quot;Gold Digger&quot; featured which Oscar-winning actor?",
            "correct_answer": "Jamie Foxx",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Alec Baldwin",
                "Dwayne Johnson",
                " Bruce Willis"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "&quot;Hallelujah&quot; is a song written by which Canadian recording artist?",
            "correct_answer": "Leonard Cohen",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Kory Lefkowits",
                "Ryan Letourneau ",
                "Justin Bieber "
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "&quot;Grande Valse&quot; is a phrase from the song &quot;Gran Vals&quot;. What is that song segment known as?",
            "correct_answer": "Nokia Tune",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Hello Moto [Motorola Ringtone]",
                "Droid Ringtone",
                "Microsoft Ringtone"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "What is the name of Rivers Cuomo&#039;s wife?",
            "correct_answer": "Kyoko Ito",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Yoko Ono",
                "Kyary Pamyu Pamyu",
                "LiSA"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "From which country did the song &quot;Gangnam Style&quot; originate from?",
            "correct_answer": "South Korea",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Japan",
                "North Korea",
                "China"
            ]
        }
    ]
}